

UX-UI and PRODUCT DESIGNER

Email : cihany@gmail.com

Portfolio: hellocihan.com

Linkedin: linkedin.com/in/cihany

+(90) 532 701 13 89

Karliktepe Mah. Adem Yavuz Sk. 26/3 Kartal - Istanbul / Turkey

About

I'm UX/UI and Product Designer with 10+ years of experience in digital agencies and corporate companies.

For the last 5 years, I've been working as a remote UX / UI designer for companies around the world.

Such as London (publing.co and Curation Zone) - Tokyo (artefact.co.jp) and Belgium (iconecwave.com).

Experience

Gordion Teknoloji

Turkey • 2016 - UX-UI and Product Designer

I'm working on the B2B and B2C product designs for the tourism industry and making it an international product

Wamo

London • 2020 - UX-UI and Product Designer

wamo is an orchestration platform that joins the dots between payments, banking and commerce solutions in just a few lines of code.

Curation Zone

London • 2018 - 2019 Consultant UX-UI and Product Designer

I've designed UI, UX and Product designs of the Curation Zone application, a startup project. Curation Zone: A brand new way to discover filmmakers; produce, test and distribute the very best videos, using AI

Iconecwave

Belgium • 2017-2018 Consultant UX-UI and Product Designer

Web application project where veterinarians and pet owners are involved and health follow-up of their pets. This project is designed for Royal Canin

Experience

Turkcell

Turkey • 2013-2016 UX-UI and Visual Designer

I worked with many in-house teams in variety of web and mobile application projects, being responsible for designing and planning.

Artefact Inc.

Tokyo • 2017-2018 Consultant UX-UI Designer

I'm giving periodic consultations on UI and UX design with Tokyo based agency.

Publing.co

London • 2016-2018 Consultant UX-UI and Product Designer

Publing collects social media posts from different sources and shows them on many different displays.

Lidya Teknoloji

Turkey • 2012-2013 UX-UI and Visual Designer

I was responsible for UI and UX designs of B2C and B2B projects in the software developing company in tourism sector.

Hisseli Harikalar

Turkey • 2007-2013 - Consultant UX-UI and Visual Designer

Served as a UI / UX and Visual designer in the company that reflects the experience of boutique agency to its customers and to be responsible for the workflow and customer side progress.

Proton Dizayn

Turkey • 2006-2007 - Web and Visual Designer

Turk Dizayn Grubu and NetBil Web

Turkey • 2000-2005 - Web and Visual Designer

Education

Abant Izzet Baysal University

Bolu - Turkey • 1997-2002

Business Administration/Management

Kartal High School

Istanbul - Turkey • 1993-1995

Social Sciences

